Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Office of the Dean of Students Records, 1915-2012
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1915-2012, UWM Archival Collection 48; 28.2 cubic ft. (40 boxes) 5 digital text files (2 MB)
  - 1. Student Organization Files, 1915-2010
    - Student Association
      - By-laws and Committee Minutes, 2008-2010 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Committee Appointments
        - 1993-2008 (Box 22, Folder 12-26)
        - Academic Units, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
        - Administrative, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 3-4)
        - Disciplinary, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
        - Faculty, 1993-2006 (Box 23, Folder 7-9)
      - Committee Requirements Documents, 1977-1993 (Box 23, Folder 10-12)
      - Committee Rosters, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Consolidated Policy Paper on Segregated Fees, 2007 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Constitution and Policies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1995-2007 (Box 35, Folder 7-13)
      - Differential Tuition, 2006-2007 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Election Complaints, 1998-2008 (Box 35, Folder 15-16)
      - Elections, 1957-1989 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Executive Committee, 1957-1990 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Executive Committee and Senate Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Faculty, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Financial Aid, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Gary Grass v. Student Association, 2000-2001 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - General Union of Palestinian Students, Palestinian Human Rights Committee, and Zionist Student Movement of the Zionist Organization of America, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Impeachment Investigation, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Independent Election Commission
        - 1996-2008 (Box 35, Folder 21-22)
        - Campaign Brochures and Election Complaints and Results, 1998-2000 (Box 35, Folder 23)
        - Cases, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 24)
        - Report, 2007-2008 (Box 35, Folder 25)
      - Internal Audit, Correspondence and Notes, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Legislation, 2003-2008 (Box 35, Folder 26-27)
      - Master Committee List, 2007-2008 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Meeting Information Packets, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 19-20)
      - Miscellaneous, 1991-2002 (Box 23, Folder 21-22)
      - Orientation
        - 1958-1989 (Box 23, Folder 23-47)
        - 1989-1991 (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
      - Planning Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 28-29)
      - Rosters and Correspondence, 1997-2001 (Box 35, Folder 30)
      - Senate
        - Acts, 1993-1999 (Box 35, Folder 31-32)
        - Agendas, 2007-2009 (Box 35, Folder 33-34)
        - Elections, 2009 (Box 35, Folder 35)
        - Finance Committee
          - Complaint, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 36)
          - Correspondence, 2000-2009 (Box 35, Folder 37-38)
          - Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
          - Minutes, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 3)
          - Women's Resource Center, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 4)
        - Legislation, 2009 (Box 36, Folder 5)
        - Meeting Summaries, 1994-2002 (Box 24, Folder 4-6)
        - Minutes, 1991-2010 (Box 24, Folder 7-19)
        - Minutes, Summaries, and Correspondence
          - 1995-2004 (Box 36, Folder 6-20)
          - 2003-2010 (Box 37, Folder 1-12)
        - Reports, 1983-1987 (Box 24, Folder 20-23)
      - Sandburg Hall Administrative Council
        - 2004-2007 (Box 39, Folder 3)
        - Case Correspondence, Documentation, and Summaries, 2004-2007 (Box 39, Folder 4-8)
        - Internal Audit Report and Memorandums, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 9)
        - Investigation, 2005-2006 (Box 39, Folder 10)
        - Registration and Senate Minutes, 2004-2005 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Social Welfare, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - Student Activity Guide, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - Student Advisory Committee, By-laws Correspondence, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Student Association Resource Center, 1982-1993 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Student Bill of Rights, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Student Court
        - Actions, 1991-1993 (Box 24, Folder 26)
        - By-laws, Decisions, and Orders, 1990-1994 (Box 37, Folder 16)
        - Campus Bible Study Complaint, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 17)
        - Case, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 12-13)
        - Cases and Correspondence, 1993-2005 (Box 37, Folder 18-25)
        - Investigations, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 26)
        - Spending Misconduct, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 13)
        - Student Court v. Independent Election Commission, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 27)
        - Student Court v. Student Senate, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - Student Election Controversy, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Student Elections, 1993-2003 (Box 38, Folder 2-3)
      - Student Email Incident, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Student Finance Advisory Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Student Housing Audit and Correspondence, 2006-2007 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Student Misconduct Investigation, 2005-2007 (Box 39, Folder 16-19)
      - Student Organization Disciplinary Review Committee
        - 1987-1992 (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - UPASS Investigation, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Student Organizations, Correspondence and Complaints, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 7-8)
      - University General, 1981-1992 (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - UWM Police Department Reports, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - Wisconsin Public Interest Research Group, 1999-2006 (Box 38, Folder 9-10)
    - Student Association for Research and Enlightenment, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Student Book Cooperative, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Student Club of the American Institute of Industrial Engineers, 1972-1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Student Coalition Against Racism, 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Student Coalition Group, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Student Committee for Landry, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Student Committee for UNICEF, 1989-1993 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Student Communication Association, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Student Concern on Relevant Engineering, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Student Coordinating Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Student Defense Coalition, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Student Disciplinary Guidelines, 1973-1979 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Student Drinkers, Inc., 1989-1992 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Student Education Association, 1963-1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Student Equality Fellowship, 1963-1967 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Student-Faculty Committee To End The War In Vietnam, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Student Film Organization of Milwaukee, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Student Front, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Student Government
      - Constitutions and Registrations, 1957-1989 (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - Resolutions, 1957-1980 (Box 24, Folder 29-30)
      - Resolutions External to the University, 1959-1990 (Box 24, Folder 31-32)
    - Student Handbook, 1992-1994 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Student Handicapped Affiliation for Recreational Enjoyment, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Student Housing Administration Council, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Student Leadership Awards, 1966-1969 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Student League for Improvement, 1971-1987 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Student Life and Interests Committee, 1965-1973 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Student Mobilization Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Student Movement for the Attainment of Consumer Knowledge, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Student Newspaper Survey, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Student Newspapers Report, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Student Nurse Organization, 1966-1983 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Student Nurses for the Awareness of Political Issues, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Student Opportunity Society, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Student Organization for Athletic Grant-in-Aid, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Student Organization for Educational Diversity, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Student Organization Handbook, 1969-1983 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Student Pharmaceutical Society, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Student Polish Cultural Club, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Student Program Committee, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Student Purity Party, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Student Religious Liberals, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Student Research & Design Group, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Student Review at UWM, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Student Socialist Forum, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Student Society for the Study of Transpersonal Psychology, 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Student Sociological Association, 1972-1981 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Student Speakers Bureau, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Student Strike, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Student Tax Association, 1986-1991 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Student Travel Club at UWM, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Student Tutorial Commission, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Student Union, 1964-1972 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Student University Debate Society, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Student Voice, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Student Workers Organizing Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Student YWCA at UWM, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Student Zionist Organization, 1959-1967 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Students Against Monopolies on Campus, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Students Against Morally Bankrupt Senators, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Students Against University Racism, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Students Agreeing with Moody, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Students Aligned for Efficiency (SAFE), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Students Coalition of Promoting Equality (SCOPE), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Students for a Better UWM, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Students for a Color-Blind Campus, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Students for a Democratic Society, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 38-40)
    - Students for a Free Latvia, 1976-1988 (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Students for a Free Market Economy, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Students for a Free Southern Africa, 1986-1988 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Students for a Libertarian Society, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Students for a More Responsive School Board, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Students for a Peaceful Society, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Students for a United Ireland, 1981-1990 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Students for Autonomy, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Students for Barb Notestein, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - Students for Baker, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Students for Bob Kasten, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Students for Braun for Congress, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Students for Bush
      - 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - 1992 (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - Students for Carpenter, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Students for Chvala, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 73)
    - Students for Child Care, 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Students for Clinton/Gore, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Students for Consistency in Government, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - Students for Conta, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 76)
    - Students for Cranston, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Students for Disarmament, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Students for Dole at UWM, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 77)
    - Students for Don Sykes, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 78)
    - Students for Donna Horowitz, 1984-1987 (Box 19, Folder 79)
    - Students for Dukakis, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 80)
    - Students for Earl, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 81)
    - Students for Economic Freedom at UWM, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Students for Eunice Edgar, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Students for Fred Kessler, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 82)
    - Students for Garvey, 1985-1988 (Box 19, Folder 83)
    - Students for Gary Hart, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Students for George McGovern, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Students for Griffin, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Students for Habitat for Humanity International, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 84)
    - Students for Hall-Davis, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Students for Honesty at UWM, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 85)
    - Students for Jerry Schulz, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Students for Jim Moody, 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Students for John Anderson, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Students for John Norquist (for Mayor), 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 86)
    - Students for Jordahl, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Students for Justice, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Students for Kasten, 1985-1992 (Box 19, Folder 87)
    - Students for Kemp, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 88)
    - Students for Kohl
      - 1988 (Box 19, Folder 89)
      - 1994 (Box 19, Folder 90)
    - Students for Koneazny, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Students for Life, 1973-1986 (Box 19, Folder 91)
    - Students for Lindsay, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Students for Mass Communication, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Students for McGovern, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Students for Nelson, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Students for Nuclear Disarmament, 1978-1990 (Box 19, Folder 92)
    - Students for Origins Research, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Students for Palestine, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Students for Patricia A. Barnes, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Students for Peace and Justice in the Middle East, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Students for Personal Growth, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Students for Positive Change, 1978-1987 (Box 19, Folder 93)
    - Students for Progressive Education, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Students for Reagan, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Students for Reagan at UWM, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Students for Reagan/Bush, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Students for Recovery, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 94)
    - Students for Reform in Food Service, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 95)
    - Students for Representative Government, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Students for Safe Fire Arms Handling, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Students for Schreiber, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Students for Schulz, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 96)
    - Students for Spring Break, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 97)
    - Students for Stacy, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Students for Stokes, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 98)
    - Students for Stower, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Students for Student Drinkers, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 99)
    - Students for Student Government Reform, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 100)
    - Students for Student Travel at UWM, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 101)
    - Students for Students, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Students for Synthetic Education, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Students for the Craft Centre, 1990-1996 (Box 19, Folder 102)
    - Students for the Draft of President Nixon, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Students for the Non-Communist Unification of Greater Germany, 1986-1990 (Box 19, Folder 103)
    - Students for Thompson, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 104)
    - Students for Tom Loftus, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 105)
    - Students for Tom Schneider, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Students for Tuition Freeze, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 106)
    - Students for Union Reform (SURE), 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 107)
    - Students for USSA at UWM, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 108)
    - Students for WSUM, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 109)
    - Students Helping for Advocacy, Rehabilitation and Education, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Students in Solidarity Against Racism Coalition, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 110)
    - Students in Support of Women's Athletics at the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Students International Mediation Society, 1970-1985 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Students Making a Responsible Tomorrow (SMART), 1993 (Box 19, Folder 111)
    - Students Making Improvements in Leadership and Education (SMILE), 1993 (Box 19, Folder 112)
    - Students Mobilized for Survival, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Students of Education, 1965-1972 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Students of Engineering and Applied Science, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Students Organize for Schmitz, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Students Organized Against Reagan (SOAR), 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 113)
    - Students Organized for Students, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 114)
    - Students Party, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 115)
    - Students' Rights Party, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Students Supporting Matt Flynn for Congress, 1985-1988 (Box 19, Folder 116)
    - Students Taking a New Direction (S.T.A.), 1988 (Box 19, Folder 117)
    - Students to Encourage Patriotism, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Students to Support Milwaukee 14, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Students United for a Strong Stand in Vietnam, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Students with a Disability (SWAD), 1992 (Box 19, Folder 118)
    - Suave (Bourgeois of Suave Intellect), 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 119)
    - Sufi Dancing, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Suhkha/Duhkha, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 120)
    - Sun, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 121)
    - Sun Party, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Sunny Goodstreet Film Society, 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Surprise Party, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 122)
    - Switchboard, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Symphonic Band, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Symphony Orchestra at UWM, 1959-1982 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - T'ai Chi Chuan Club, 1974-1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - T'ai Chi Club, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Tae Kwon Do Association, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 123)
    - Tae Kwon Do Club, 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Tai Ju Body Sense, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 124)
    - Tailgunners at UWM, 1992-1994 (Box 19, Folder 125)
    - Taiwanese Student Association, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Talent, Inc. Talisman, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Tamal Students Association, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 126)
    - Target Medical Doctor Association, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 127)
    - TASK [Teamwork and Student Knowledge], 1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Task Force for Implementation of Student Disciplinary Guidelines on UWM Campus, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Task Force on the Status of Women in Student Affairs at UWM, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Tau Kappa Epsilon, 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Tau Omega, 1967-1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Tax Association, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 128)
    - Tea Totallers Social Club, 1975-1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Teaching of the Ascended Masters, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Tempest/Cheshire Literary Magazine
      - 1957-1974 (Box 8, Folder 13-14)
      - Activities, 1962-1971 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Financial Records, 1969-1973 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Tenant Resource Organization, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Tennessee Jed's Film Society, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Terminal Velocity, Airbourne Activities, and Skydiving Club, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 129)
    - Termpaper Companies, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Thai Association, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Theatre Etc., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Theatre Student Association, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Theta Phi Mu, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Theta Sigma Phi, 1966-1971 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Theta Sigma Upsilon, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Theta Xi, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Third Coast Design Coop, 1983-1987 (Box 19, Folder 130)
    - Third Coast Group, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Third World Tuju Club, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - TKB Social Club, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 131)
    - Today's Special, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 132)
    - Tony Earl for Governor Campaign, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Travel Club at UWM, 1991-1994 (Box 19, Folder 133)
    - Tri Sigma, 1949-1967 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Triangle Fraternity, 1961-1963 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Triathlon Club, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Truth Encounter, 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Tupperware Party, 1972-1975 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Turkish Student Association, 1977-1988 (Box 19, Folder 134)
    - U. S.-China People's Friendship Association, 1978-1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - U. S. Committee for Justice to Latin American Political Prisoners, 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - U. S. Labor Party, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - U. S. Tamburello Sport Club, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 153)
    - Udall for President, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - U-Fest, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Ukrainian Club, 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Ultimate Club, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 135)
    - Unification Church, 1974-1980 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Union Employees Association, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 136)
    - Union for Democratic Socialism, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Union for Social Action, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Union of Progressive Student Media, 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 137)
    - Union of Progressive Students, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Union Vodvil, 1920-1921 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - United Black Student Front, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - United Campus Christian Fellowship, 1960-1967 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - United Crafts Center, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - United Farmworkers Support Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - United Gay Students at UWM, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - United Greek Council at UWM, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 138)
    - United Greek Letter Organization Council, 1982-1985 (Box 19, Folder 139)
    - United Ministry in Higher Education, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - United Student Alliance
      - 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 45)
      - 1980-1985 (Box 19, Folder 140)
    - United Student Fellowship, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - United Student Sociological Society, 1982-1985 (Box 19, Folder 141)
    - United Students' Alliance at UWM, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 142)
    - United Students Coalition, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - United We Stand for America, UWM Chapter, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 143)
    - Unity, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 144)
    - University Aquarium Club, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 145)
    - University Brass Ensemble, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - University Bridge Club, 1979-1990 (Box 19, Folder 146)
    - University Civil Liberties Union, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - University Committee Against the Draft, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - University Committee to Save North Division High School, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - University Democratic Alliance, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - University Forum Organization, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - University Marketing, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 147)
    - University Players, 1957-1971 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - University Political Action Council, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - University Productions, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 148)
    - University Religious Council, 1954-1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - University Scottish Society, 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - University Ski Team, 1988-1992 (Box 19, Folder 149)
    - University Student Government, 1956-1974 (Box 8, Folder 56-64)
    - University Students' Committee, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - University Symphony Orchestra, 1957-1963 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - University Typing Services, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - University Velo Club, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - University Wheelmen, 1975-1992 (Box 19, Folder 150)
    - University Women's Council, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Unix Bombsquad, 1982-1993 (Box 19, Folder 151)
    - The Unnamed Social Club, 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Upward Bound, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Urban Planning Students Organization, 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Urban Social Institutions Student Organization, 1982-1990 (Box 19, Folder 152)
    - Urban Studies Club, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - US, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 154)
    - Users of IBM/PS 2, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 155)
    - Using Union Policies Better for Students, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 156)